She's crawling! Emma's crawling!
她在爬！艾□在爬了！
He's bleeding! Joey's bleeding!
他在流血！喬伊在流血了！
I'm sorry. You've gotta see this. I'm gonna go get Monica and Chandler.
對不起，但你一定要來看 我去找摩妮卡跟錢德
Monica! Chandler!
摩妮卡！錢德！
Come over! Come over! Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
過來！過來！快點、快點、快點！
What? What?
怎樣？什麼事？
- Shaving? - No, rabies.
-刮鬍子嗎？ -不，狂犬病
- What's going on? - It's Emma. She's crawling.
-是怎麼回事？ -是艾□，她會爬了
Wow, look at her go.
哇，瞧瞧她
Give her a second.
給她一點時間
-Joey, Joey. -Oh, sorry.
-喬伊，喬伊 -哦，對不起
I can't believe how fast she's growing up. It seems like only yesterday she was..
我真不敢相信她長的好快 好像昨天她才…
farting on my lap.
在我腿上放屁
Not so funny when someone does that to you, is it?
有人對你那樣做的時候 並不好笑吧？
Emma, come on. Show everybody how you were crawling.
艾□，來吧，讓大家看看你會爬了
Come on, Emma.
-艾□，來吧 -爬呀，艾□
I think we're distracting her. Let's everybody be still for a minute.
我想我們讓她分心了 大家先一分鐘不要動
Who's painting us?
誰在畫我們呢？
The One With The Boob Job
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Have you seen our bank statement? Can this be right?
你有看過我們的銀行對帳單了嗎？ 沒錯嗎？
I know. God, I haven't seen my savings take a hit like this..
就是嘛，天啊 我的存款就沒這麼少過…
since I was a kid and they came up with Double Stuf Oreos.
自從我小時候雙層夾心餅上市之後
- What happened to all of our money? - I'm not sure exactly what they did..
-我們的錢跑哪去了呢？ -我不清楚他們做了什麼…
but I'm inclined to blame Enron.
但是我傾向於責怪恩隆案
With you doing the internship, we're spending more than we're bringing in.
因為你在做實習工作 我們花的比賺的還多
Yeah, maybe I should quit and get a job that pays.
是啊，或許我應該辭掉 然後找個有薪水的工作
But you're finally doing something that you love.
但是你終於找到你喜歡的工作了
I mean, I can't ask you to give that up.
我是說，我不能要求你放棄的
Although it would be nice if the thing that you loved was finding gold.
不過如果你喜歡做的事 是尋寶，那會好多了
You know, I think we're making too big a deal out of this.
我覺得我們太小題大作了
We'll pay our bills late this month. Next month we'll cut back on a few things.
我們這個月會比較緊 下個月我們就節省一些開銷
And maybe we start eating out of Joey's refrigerator for a change.
而且或許我們可以改變一下 到喬伊家的冰箱找食物
You're a chef. What can you make out of baking soda and beer?
你是廚師 你可以用蘇打粉跟啤酒做出什麼呢？
Worst-case scenario is, we borrow some money from my parents.
最糟糕的情況下，我們只好我父母借錢
Or, you slipped on ice at their house last month. Can we sue them?
或者，你上個月在他們家溜冰滑倒 我們可以告他們嗎？
No, and we're not borrowing money.
不可以，而且我們也不借錢
- Why not? - We don't do that. We are Bings.
-為什麼不行？ -我們不能那樣做，我們是賓家的人
If there's one thing my father taught me, it was..
我爸有教過我
well, to always knock before going into the pool house.
在進入撞球間時一定要先敲門
- The other thing is, never borrow money. - I had no idea you had this much pride.
-還有，永遠都不要借錢 -我不知道你是如此有榮譽感
That's right, I do. I am your man. I'm gonna get us through this situation..
沒錯，我就是，我是你男人 我會讓我們度過難關的
even if it means you working twice as hard.
就算要你加倍努力工作也是
You know, it's just really weird.
你知道嗎？真的是很奇怪
You don't like eating animals, but you love watching them tear each other apart.
你不喜歡吃動物 卻喜歡看他們彼此廝殺
No, I don't.. Get him. Get him!
不，我不喜歡…抓住他，抓他！
Separate the sick one from the herd!
把病倒的那個從群體隔開！
- I'm gonna go. - Why?
-我要回去了 -為什麼？
I haven't been home in days, and I need to get more clothes.
我有好幾天沒有回家了 而且我需要多拿幾件衣服
You don't have to go. I have something that'll fit you.
你不用回去，我有衣服可以給你穿
I put that tube top on as a joke.
我穿女生的緊身衣是為了要好笑
- I want you to stay. - I want to stay too.
-我想要你留下來 -我也想要留下來
But I've got as much use out of these boxers as I can.
但是我已經不能再穿這幾件內褲了
- Why don't you turn them inside.. - Done it.
-為什麼不反過來再穿呢？ -已經反過了
- I'll be back in a couple of hours. - All right. I'll miss you.
-我幾個小時之後就回來 -好吧，我會想你的
Me too.
我也是
Oh, fine. Yeah, you got away.
喔，好啦，你是逃走了
But don't look so smug. You're gonna bleed to death.
但是不要太沾沾自喜 你會失血過多而死的
You know what? I just realized something. I don't want to go home.
你知道嗎？我剛驚覺到一件事 我不想要回家
- Great! Okay, I'll go get the tube top. - No, no, what I mean is..
-太好了，好的，我去拿緊身衣 -不，我的意思是…
I hate going back to my apartment now.
我不喜歡回去自己的公寓
Partly because I live above a known crack den..
一方面是因為我住在 一間髒亂的小房間上面
but, you know, mostly because when I'm there, I really miss you.
但是，主要是因為我回去的時候 我真的好想你
So..
所以…
do you want to move in together?
我們一起住好不好？
Wow, Mike Hanigan..
哇，麥克漢尼根
you sure know how to make a girl say "Hell, yeah."
你倒是挺清楚要如何 讓女生說「好！」
- So we're doing it? - Yeah, let's do it. Let's live together.
-那我們要這樣做嗎？ -好啊，就這樣做，我們一起住
- We're really gonna move in together? - Yeah.
-我們真的要同居嗎？ -是啊
I've always wanted to live with a guy.
我一直都想要跟男生同居
Pick up your socks. Put down the toilet seat.
襪子撿起來，馬桶坐墊放下來
No, we are not having sex anymore.
不，我再也不跟你做愛了
It's gonna be fun.
一定會很好玩
Shame on you, TV Guide.
真討厭《電視指南》
A man's ass is not nudity!
男人的屁股不算是裸露！
- Hey, Joey. - Hey.
-嘿，喬伊 -嘿
Listen, I need to know that what I'm about to ask you..
聽著，我需要你保證 我接下來要問你的事…
will never get back to Chandler.
不會被錢德知道
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't thought about it myself.
如果說我沒有想過那件事 我就是在說謊
But Chandler is my best friend. It would be wrong.
但是錢德是我最好的朋友 那是不對的
Good, but wrong.
感覺不錯，卻是不對的
Okay, first of all, it would be great.
好的，首先，感覺會是棒透了
But that's not what I'm here to talk to you about. I need to borrow money.
但那不是我在想的事 我需要跟你借錢
Oh, I don't know, Monica. You know..
喔，我不知道，摩妮卡，你知道的
lending friends money is always a mistake.
借錢給朋友不是什麼好事
- But Chandler lent you money. - And he would tell you it was a mistake.
-但是錢德借過你錢啊 -而他也會告訴你，那不是什麼好事
Come on, I just.. I need it for some rent and some other bills.
別這樣，我只是… 我需要付房租跟一些帳單
Well, how much?
多少錢呢？
- Two thousand dollars? - Two thousand dollars?
-兩千塊 -兩千塊？
What do you think I am, a soap opera star?
你以為我是誰？肥皂劇明星嗎？
- Yeah. - That's right, I am.
-是啊 -沒錯，我就是
Promise me you'll never tell Chandler.
答應我，你不會告訴錢德
It'll really hurt his pride.
這真的會很傷他的自尊心
Chandler? Pride?
錢德？自尊心？
I know, he thinks he has it. It's really cute.
我知道，他還以為他有 真的是很可愛
- Hi, you guys. - Hey.
-嗨，你們好 -嘿
- What's in the bag? - You know how Emma started crawling?
-袋子裡面是什麼？ -你們都知道艾□已經開始會爬了
I realized that this place is very unsafe for a baby..
我發現這地方對嬰兒而言 是很不安全的
so I went to the store and I got some stuff to baby-proof the apartment.
所以我去店裡買了一些東西 來讓公寓更適合嬰兒活動
Oh, God, baby-proofing.
喔，天啊，適合嬰兒
Why is it such a big deal now? You know, when I was a kid, it was like:
有什麼了不起的呢？ 我小的時候，常常都…
"Whoops, Joey fell down the stairs."
「哇，喬伊跌下樓梯了」
Or, "Whoops, Joey electrocuted himself again."
或是「哇，喬伊又電到自己了」
Anyway, are you going to get a handyman to install this stuff?
你要找人幫忙安裝這些東西嗎？
No, I was just gonna do it myself.
不，我自己來就行了
- You're gonna do it? - Yeah. Why?
-你要自己來？ -是啊，不行嗎？
- You don't think a woman can do this? - Women can. You can't.
-你覺得女人不可能自己做嗎？ -女人可以，你不行
Monica, will you please tell Joey that he is a pig.
摩妮卡，可以請你告訴喬伊 他是豬嗎？
- You're a pig. And you can't do this. - What?
-你是豬，而你不會做 -什麼？
What? Come on, I found the hardware store all by myself.
別這樣，我自己找到五金店的
The store's right down the street.
那間店就在街尾
There is a hardware store right down the street?
街尾就有一間五金店嗎？
Hey, you guys? Okay, we've got great news.
嘿，各位，我們有好消息要宣佈
- Phoebe and I are moving in together. - Congratulations.
-菲比跟我要同居了 -恭喜了
I know, it's so exciting. You know, I've never lived with a guy before.
我知道，好興奮 我從來都沒有跟男生同居過
Well, it's just like living with a girl, only they don't steal your makeup.
嗯，那就像跟女生一起住一樣 只是他們不會偷用你的化妝品
Unless they're playing "This Is What My Sister Would Look Like."
除非他們是在玩 「我妹妹就是長這樣」
Yeah, she's not so cute.
是啊，她不太可愛
- I'm gonna go to the bathroom. - Well, you put down the toilet seat.
-我要上洗手間 -上完把馬桶坐墊放下來
Yes, dear.
是的，親愛的
- Is that a bit you guys do? - Uh-huh. We're playing you two.
-那是你們在玩的遊戲嗎？ -是啊，我們在模仿你們倆個
We don't do that. Tell her we don't do that.
我們沒有那樣，告訴她我們沒有
Yes, dear.
我們有，親愛的
I can't believe you're moving in together. I'm happy for you guys.
不敢相信你們要同居了 我真替你們高興
I mean, he's a great catch. And those eyes..
我是說，他是個好對像 而且那一雙眼睛…
I'm a scientist. I observe.
我是科學家，我會觀察
Gosh, this is so exciting! You guys are really moving along.
天啊，這真是太令人興奮了！ 你們真是交往的太順利了
- I hear wedding bells. - Monica, slow down, okay?
-我聽到婚禮進行曲了 -摩妮卡，別急好嗎？
I'm just excited to be living with him.
我只是很興奮要跟他一起住而已
You know, I mean, I don't know..
你知道的，我是說，我不知道…
can I see someday being married to Mike? Sure. Yeah.
我能預見有天跟麥克結婚嗎？ 是的，當然
I could picture myself walking down the aisle in a wedding dress..
我可以想像自己 穿著婚紗走在紅毯上
that highlights my breasts in an obvious yet classy way.
婚紗以很明顯、但高雅的方式 集中突出我的胸部
But do I want that house in Connecticut near the good schools..
但問我想不想要在康乃狄克州 有好學區的房子…
where Mike and I could send little Sophie and Mike Jr.?
讓麥克跟我送我們的 小蘇菲跟小麥克去上學？
Oh, my God, I do.
喔，我的天，我好想
- I had no idea you were so conventional. - I know. I guess I am.
-我不曉得你是這麼傳統的人 -我想我是的
Oh, my God, load up the Volvo, I want to be a soccer mom.
我的天，開著富豪汽車 大包小包載孩子去練足球
- You ready to go? - Yeah, you bet, roomie.
-你準備好要走了嗎？ -當然好囉，新室友
Don't you mean "groomie"?
你是說「新郎」吧
Honey, leave the terrible jokes to me.
親愛的，把爛笑話留給我吧
- What are you talking about? - Please.
-你在說什麼？ -拜託
We haven't even moved in yet, and they have us picking out china patterns.
我們都還沒一起住 而他們就要我們選結婚禮物了
China patterns!
結婚禮物！
This is easy. "Can't do this.."
這很容易的，「你不行…」
Wow, seriously. Can't do this.
哇，還真的咧，就是不行
（中央咖啡廳）
- Hey, Joe. - Hey.
-嘿，喬伊 -嘿
You here with somebody?
你有跟別人在這裡嗎？
No.
沒有
Look, I need to ask you a favor, and we can't tell Monica anything about it.
聽著，我需要你幫個忙 而且不能跟摩妮卡說
- I thought you guys didn't have secrets. - That will remain the official party line.
-我以為你們之間沒有秘密 -表面上是那樣沒錯
Look, Monica and I are having a little financial trouble.
摩妮卡跟我有一點點經濟上的問題
- Yeah, I know. - What? What do you mean, you "know"?
-是啊，我知道 -什麼？你是什麼意思？
I just figured it out, you know?
我猜的，你知道的
I mean, you're not working, and the economy is bad.
我是說，你沒有工作 而且現在經濟又很蕭條
Oh, right.
喔，對
That is the fastest I have ever thought.
這是我反應最快的一次了
Anyway..
反正…
I need to borrow some money.
我需要跟你借點錢
Oh, sure. Yeah, how much? Two thousand dollars?
當然囉，多少錢？兩千塊嗎？
Yes, $2000 exactly. How did you know that?
是的，正是兩千塊 你是怎麼知道的？
I know how much you used to make, and I know how much your rent is.
我知道你之前賺多少錢 而且我也知道你們的房租
Oh, okay.
喔，好的
I am on fire.
我真是天才
Listen, this is really nice.
聽著，你真好
Did you write a check to Monica for $2000?
你開一張兩千塊的支票給摩妮卡？
Did Monica borrow money from you?
摩妮卡跟你借錢？
- Kind of. - I can't believe her.
-好像是 -我不敢相信她竟然這樣做
Did she tell you we were having money problems?
她有跟你說我們有經濟問題嗎？
No, no, no. It wasn't because of your money problems.
不，不是為了你們的經濟問題
It was for something for her.
是她自己的東西
What?
什麼？
Something personal.
很私人的東西
What would she get for $2000 that she wouldn't tell me about?
她要花兩千塊的東西還不能告訴我？
Excuse me.
不好意思
Boob job.
隆乳手術
What? That's ridiculous. She doesn't need a boob job.
什麼？這真是太可笑了 她才不需要隆乳
Why wouldn't she tell me about it?
她為什麼不能告訴我呢？
She was afraid you wouldn't be supportive.
她怕你會反對
- I'm not. - She knows you well.
-我是會，沒錯 -她非常瞭解你
You can't tell her that you know. I swore I wouldn't tell.
你不能告訴她你已經知道了 我發過誓不會告訴別人的
A boob job? She doesn't need that. That's crazy.
隆乳手術？她根本不需要 這真是瘋狂
Well, it's not that crazy, okay?
不算太瘋狂，好嗎？
Making them smaller, that would be crazy.
把咪咪變小才叫做瘋狂
Hey, so where do you keep your secret box of porn?
嘿，你的秘密色情影帶放哪兒？
I don't have any porn.
我沒有什麼色情影帶
Back of the closet in my bedroom.
我房間後面的櫃子裡
Oh, hey, I wanted to ask you about Monica's little "groomie" joke.
嘿，我想要問你關於 摩妮卡的「新郎」笑話
Well, I think the reason people laughed is that it's a play on the word "roomie."
我想大家會笑 是因為她在玩「新室友」這個詞
I get the joke. Sophisticated as it was.
我聽得懂這個笑話，真是高深啊
No, the thing I want to say is..
不，我要說的是…
Maybe we should've talked about this before.
或許我們之前就應該先談過
Us living together, you're not expecting a proposal, right?
我們住在一起這件事 你應該沒有期望我會求婚吧
- Oh, no, no. Not at all. - Okay.
-喔，不、不，一點也沒有 -好的
We're just moving in right now. We'll see where it goes.
我們才剛搬進來一起住，再看看吧
Yeah, well, that's the thing. For me, it's as far as it can ever go.
對，這就是個問題 對我而言，這已經是我的極限了
- What do you mean? - Look, Phoebe, I..
-你是什麼意思？ -聽著，菲比，我…
I love you very much. But I never want to get married again.
我非常愛你，但我不想再結婚了
- Wow. - It's just, my first marriage was..
-哇 -只是我的第一次婚姻太…
you know, such a disaster that I kind of lost faith in the whole idea.
太糟糕了，我已經對婚姻失去信心了
- Was it that bad? - At one point, near the end..
-有那麼糟嗎？ -有一次，到最後…
- she deliberately defecated on my.. - Okay, well, that's bad. Yeah.
-她故意便便在我的… -喔，那真糟
But don't you think it might be different with someone else? Perhaps..
但是你不認為換個人會不一樣嗎？
a blond who always uses the toilet?
或許是一個會在廁所便便的金髮女郎？
Except for once in the ocean.
除了有一次便在海裡
Look, it's not about who I would marry.
聽著，不是我要娶誰的問題
I was certain the first time I got married it'd last forever. I was wrong.
我本來也確定我第一次的婚姻 會維持永遠，我錯了
- But, it just.. - Look, Phoebe, it's not about you.
-但是，只是… -菲比，不是你的原因
I just never want to get married again.
我只是再也不想結婚了
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Are you okay with that? If not, maybe us moving in together isn't the best idea.
你可以接受嗎？如果不行的話 或許我們一起住不是個好主意
No. Oh, I definitely don't want to get married.
可以，喔，我當然也不希望結婚
I just wanted to make sure you didn't want to, too.
我只想確定你也不想要
Because if we move in and you start changing your mind..
因為如果我們住在一起 然後你開始改變心意…
there is gonna be hell to pay, mister.
我們就有麻煩了，先生
- Trust me. I will never.. - Yeah, I get that. Yeah.
-相信我，我永遠不… -好的，我知道了
Hi. So you gave in and decided to call someone?
嗨，最後你決定請人來幫忙了？
Yeah. I don't know who I was kidding. I can barely use chopsticks.
是啊，我不知道我是在想什麼 我連筷子都不會用
- You're all set. - Oh, thank you so much.
-都裝好了 -喔，真的很謝謝你
Wait. You forgot your..
等等，你忘了你的…
game.
玩具
Thank you.
謝謝你
- Rach, is this my sweater? - Yeah.
-瑞秋，這是我的線衫嗎？ -是啊
What happened to the sleeve?
袖子怎麼了呢？
Moths?
蛀蟲嗎？
Hey, Rach. There she is, my perfectly proportioned wife.
嘿，瑞秋 我身材完美的老婆在這裡
Don't look at me. I never get his jokes.
別看我，我從來沒有聽懂過他的笑話
- Thank you? - No, no. Don't thank me.
-謝謝你 -不、不，別謝我
Thank you. Do you know there is not one thing I would change about you?
謝謝你，你知道我不會想要 改變你任何一點嗎？
Not one single thing. And definitely not..
一點也沒有，而且特別是…
two single things.
那兩點
Okay, you're being weird. Do you want sex, or did you do something bad?
好的，你真的很怪 你想上床嗎？還是做了什麼錯事？
No. No. No. I just love the way you look. I am warm..
不、不、不，我就是愛你這模樣 我愛你的…
for your form.
身材
Okay, you know the old classics like, you know, "You look nice"?
好的，你知道傳統上都是說 「你看起來很好」吧？
They're still okay.
這句話還是適用
But "you look nice" could mean that I'm saying, "Your face looks nice."
但是「你看起來很好」可能只是代表 「你的臉蛋看起來很好」
I want to compliment your body.
我想要讚美你的身體
I mean, I wouldn't change it at all.
我是說，我一點都不想改變它
And more specifically, I wouldn't want anything to get any bigger.
而且更詳細地說，就是 我不想要加大任何東西
- Okay. - I mean..
-好的 -我是說…
you wouldn't want any part of me to get any bigger, would you?
你也不會想要我身體的某部份加大 不是嗎？
Don't answer that.
不用回答
Just when you thought that dude couldn't get any weirder.
我還以為那老兄不可能更怪了
Why do you think he was so worried about me getting bigger?
你覺得他為何要擔心我會變大？
I don't know. I mean, what brought that on?
我不知道，那是怎麼回事呢？
Oh, my God. You know what, we're trying to get pregnant..
我的天，你知道嗎？ 我們正努力要懷孕…
so he's probably starting to freak out that my body's gonna change.
所以他可能很怕我的身材會變形
- You think that's what it is? - You heard him.
-你認為是這樣嗎？ -你也看到了
"No bigger. You're perfect. Just don't get any bigger."
「不要變大，你很完美了 不要再變大了」
My God, he sounded just like my high-school wrestling coach.
天啊，他聽起來就像是 我高中的摔角教練
- I'm gonna have to talk to Chandler. - Yeah. If you don't, I will.
-我必須要跟錢德談談 -是啊，如果你不去，我會去
Of course your body's gonna change. Your breasts are gonna get bigger..
當然你的身材會變形 你的胸部會變大
your ass is gonna get bigger..
你的屁股會變大
you're gonna lose bladder control.
你會膀胱無力
God, it's just such a magical time.
我的天，真是奇妙啊
Hi. Listen, I wanted to ask you something about marriage.
嗨，聽著，我想要請教你關於婚姻的事
Now you're seeking me out to make jokes?
現在你跑來找我，是要取笑我嗎？
I mean, I can see if we're all hanging out, but to come to my home..
我們出去在一起的時候被取笑 我可以理解，但是跑到我家來…
No, I really want to know how you feel about it.
不，我真的想知道你的意見
- Why? - Mike doesn't ever want to get married.
-為什麼？ -麥克永遠不想再結婚了
- Never? - Never.
-永遠嗎？ -永遠
Wow. Are you still gonna move in with him?
哇，你還要跟他同居嗎？
I want to, but I wanted you to tell me that marriage really isn't that big a deal.
我想啊，但是我要你告訴我 結婚真的不算什麼
You know, that I won't be missing out on anything. That marriage stinks.
沒結婚也不必後悔，婚姻爛斃了
Yeah, marriage stinks.
是啊，婚姻爛斃了
I mean, if you want to see a man gain weight and a woman stop shaving..
我是說，如果你想看到男人變肥 女人不再除毛…
get them married.
就叫他們結婚吧
- That's not how you really feel, is it? - No, I'm sorry.
-那不是你真正的感覺，對吧 -不是，我很抱歉
I know it's not what you want to hear, but I can't help it. I love marriage.
我知道那不是你想聽的話 但是我沒有辦法說謊，我喜歡結婚
Seriously, you? "Divorce-o"?
真的嗎？你這個「離婚專家」？
If you have to call me a name, I'd prefer "Ross, the Divorcer." It's just cooler.
如果你要幫我取綽號，我比較喜歡 「羅斯，離婚王」，聽起來較酷
Look, I know my marriages didn't exactly work out..
聽著，我知道我的婚姻並沒有成功
but, you know, I loved being that committed to another person.
但我喜歡對另一個人做那種程度的承諾
And Carol and I had some good times before she became a lesbian.
在凱羅變成女同性戀之前 我們度過許多快樂的時光
And once afterward.
之後還有一次
Anyway, I'm sorry.
反正，很抱歉
It's okay. That's how you feel.
沒關係，這是你的真實感受
But, come on, I mean, living together will be great.
但是，別這樣，住在一起也很棒阿
I mean, you guys have so much fun. And you love Mike.
我是說你們會很快樂的 而且你愛麥克啊
- I do love Mike. - Yeah, see?
-我是很愛麥克 -是啊，不是嗎？
And you were so excited about moving in together before..
而且你之前很期待同居的
and you know what, you should be. It's a big deal.
而且你知道嗎？期待是對的 這是很大的一步
Yeah, I guess you're right.
是啊，我想你說的對
Yeah, thanks. This helped. Thanks.
是啊，謝謝，真有幫助，謝謝
The Divorcer to the rescue.
離婚王拯救眾生
- It's not cooler. - Yeah, I just heard it.
-並沒有比較酷 -我聽到了
Rach?
瑞秋？
Rachel?!
瑞秋！
So I can't do anything I like?!
所以我想做什麼都不行嗎？
Unbelievable.
不可思議
Chandler wants you to have a baby, but he doesn't want your body to change.
錢德要你生小孩 但是不許你身材變形
It's not like he's so perfect.
他自己又不是多完美
- Hey, that's my husband. - All right.
-嘿，他是我老公 -好吧
Let's solve one problem at a time.
我們一次解決一個問題
Hey, Rach.
嘿，瑞秋
Perfection. Wouldn't change a thing. Not a thing.
完美，什麼都不必改變，完美無缺
- Honey? - Yeah?
-親愛的 -怎樣？
About that.
關於那件事
- I'm going to change. - Yes, but, honey, you don't have to.
-我會變的 -是的，但是親愛的，你不需要
I'm gonna get bigger.
我會變得大一點
Honey, I..
親愛的，我…
I love your breasts the way they are.
我喜歡你胸部現在的樣子
Fascist.
大男人
My breasts are gonna get bigger whether you like it or not.
我的胸部會變大的，不管你喜不喜歡
And it's not just my breasts. My ass is gonna get bigger too.
而且不只是我的胸部 我的屁股也會變大
Your ass?!
你的屁股？
And don't be surprised if her hands and her feet get bigger too.
而且如果她的手腳也變大，別太驚訝
- They do that? - It's kind of a package deal.
-他們也會嗎？ -這就像整套的一樣
God, why? Why would you want to do that to yourself?
天啊，為什麼？ 為什麼你要對自己做這種事呢？
I thought it was something that we both wanted.
我以為這是我們倆都想要的
If it means that much to you, I may be able to get onboard with the boobs..
如果這對你那麼重要 關於胸部，我或許可以釋懷
but the giant ass and the big clown feet?
但是大屁股還有大腳丫？
Oh, my God, Chandler.
喔，天啊，錢德
If you can't handle this, what will you be like in the hospital..
如果你連這個都受不了 那你到了醫院要怎麼辦…
with the blood and screaming and the little person that's shooting out of her?
加上流血和尖叫聲，還有那個 從她身體擠出來的小小人？
What?
什麼？
Joey, why did you tell Chandler that Monica was getting a boob job?
喬伊，你為什麼要跟錢德說 摩妮卡要去做隆乳手術呢？
Because she is.
因為她是要啊
- Chandler knows I borrowed the money. - For your boob job.
-錢德知道我跟你借錢了 -為了要做隆乳手術
- Joe.. - It's over.
-喬伊 -結束了
Okay, so I'm out $4000 and nobody's boobs are getting any bigger?
好了，所以我借出了四千塊 結果沒有人的胸部會變大？
Hey. Hey, what do you guys think about this: Ross, the Divorce Force.
嘿，嘿，你們覺得這樣如何呢？ 羅斯，離婚強棒
- Better. - Yeah?
-比較好了 -是嗎？
Very cool.
非常酷
Hey, Phoebe? You know, I'm really glad you came to talk to me the other day..
嘿，菲比 我真的很高興那天你過來找我談
- and I hope I was a little helpful. - Yeah, you were helpful.
-希望我有幫上忙 -是啊，你幫忙很多
- Yeah. No, thank you. - Good. Good.
-是啊，很謝謝你 -很好，很好
Because the more I thought about it, the more I realized..
因為我越想越覺得…
I don't think marriage is necessarily the right path for you.
婚姻對你而言，不見得是必經之路
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思？
I know the other day in the coffeehouse..
我知道那天在咖啡屋的時候…
you were all caught up in the whole soccer-mom thing..
你很沉醉於當足球媽媽什麼的
but is that really you? I mean, can you honestly picture yourself in a Volvo?
但是那是真的你嗎？ 你可以想像自己開著富豪汽車嗎？
They are awfully boxy.
富豪汽車是太有稜有角了
People like me like stability and security. You don't.
像我這樣的人才需要安定感 你不需要
And that's what's so incredible about you.
而這就是你很了不起的地方
You got this wild and crazy life.
你有狂放不羈的生活
I mean, I don't know, you'd be so bored with marriage. I mean, it's so normal.
我是說，婚姻對你是很無趣的 我是說，那太中規中矩了
Yeah.
是啊
Hey, can I help?
嘿，需要幫忙嗎？
Well, we climbed up four flights of stairs, maneuvered a narrow hallway..
我們爬了四層樓 好不容易通過狹窄的通道
dodged a rabid pit bull. But these last three feet are where it gets really tricky.
再躲過一隻狂犬病鬥牛狗 但是最後這三尺路才是最崎嶇的
You know, sometimes your words, they hurt.
有時候你的話真傷人
Hey, where do you guys want this?
嘿，你們要把這個放哪呢？
Yeah, seriously, because this is really heavy.
是啊，快點，因為真的很重
I mean, not for me, because I'm only pretending to hold it, but for these guys.
不是對我，因為我只是假裝扶著 但是他們幾個真的快被重死了
Just one last time on the marriage thing. There's no wiggle room? None at all?
最後再問你一次結婚的事 沒有再思考的空間嗎？一點都沒有？
No, but you don't want to get married either, right?
沒有，但你也不想結婚，不是嗎？
Right.
沒錯
Except that I do want to get married.
此外，我是真的想要結婚
Couldn't have had this conversation down at the truck, huh?
不能在樓下卸貨前先談這個嗎？
What? You want to get married?
什麼？你想要結婚？
Someday.
總有一天
And.. hernia.
還有…疝氣
I haven't had a normal life. And I never felt like I was missing out on anything.
我從未有過正常的生活 而我也從沒有覺得失去過什麼
But it feels like now it's my turn to have some of the regular stuff.
但是總覺得好像 該輪到我擁有正常的東西了
Why didn't you say something before?
你為什麼不早說呢？
I didn't know how much I wanted it. And I love you, and I wanted to live with you.
我之前不確定我有多想要，而且我愛你 我想要跟你一起住
I want to live with you too. I mean, let's do that.
我也想跟你一起住，我們就這樣做吧
But I don't think I can.
但是我覺得我做不到
It was okay to move in when I didn't know what was gonna happen.
當我不清楚未來時 我們是可以一起住的
But I can't move in knowing nothing is ever gonna happen.
但在知道將來什麼事都不會發生之後 我就沒辦法了
I said to bring the cushions up first, but no.
我說先搬椅墊，你們就不要
Can we at least try living together? You might change your mind about marriage.
我們可以至少先試試同居吧？ 你或許會改變對婚姻的想法
Are you gonna change yours?
你會改變你的想法嗎？
No.
不會
Me neither.
我也不會
I think I need to be with someone who wants what I want.
我想我需要跟想法一樣的人在一起
But I don't want this to end.
但是我不想要結束
No, I don't want it to end either.
我也不想要結束
I can't believe this is gonna end.
我不敢相信就要這樣結束了
I guess I'll have my stuff picked up.
我會把我的東西打包好
Yeah. Okay.
好的
Okay, so..
好的，那麼…
Goodbye.
再見
- Take it easy, Mike. - Bye, Mike.
-再見，麥克 -拜，麥克
I'm so sorry, Phoebe.
我很難過，菲比
We're all sorry.
我們都很難過
Look on the bright side. At least you won't have to live with this ugly chair.
往好處想 至少你不用跟那張丑椅子在一起
That was here already, huh?
那早就在這裡了，對不對？
I love you.
我愛你
I did it! I did it!
我辦到了！我辦到了！
All right.
太好了
I'd better take all I can carry.
最好拿多一點
Who knows when I'll be able to get in here again, huh?
誰知道下次能不能打得開呢？